genesissuppliesinc.ca 2018-08-16

# Privacy Policy

Genesis Supplies Inc., is the sole owner of Genesissuppliesinc.com and ali the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations and order status updates. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as your credit card number. We also require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your user name and password remain confidential DO NOT share this information with anyone. If you elect to receive our newsletter or special promotions, your contact information will be used for the delivery of this information.

In order to process your orders placed on this website, you must first complete the registration form to become an approved Customer. During registration, you will be required to provide your contact information, which includes your Company/Contact name, e-mail address, telephone number and main/billing address. This information is used to provide you with important Genesissuppliesinc.com services and promotions and product updates.

Most of the information collected in the registration process will be used to process orders. During the order process, you will have to provide financial information such as your credit card number, expiration date, money order，wire transfer or cheque information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. To property process your credit card information, we must share your personal and financial information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties, except those specified in the Sharing section of this policy.

We customize our Web page content based upon your browser type and other information provided by our cookie. If you choose to reject the cookie, you can still browse our site but will be unable to use the shopping cart to buy merchandise. The Genesissuppliesinc.com shopping cart cannot function without cookies enabled so that the necessary information to process your order is retained. If you disable cookies, Genesissuppliesinc.com will be unable to accept your online order. We will not share any personally identifiable information provided by this cookie with any third party. We will however, link data stored in cookies to the personally identifiable information you submitted white on our site. This aWows us to personalize your online experience and discern user preferences to evoke subconscious feelings of familiarity and assurance.

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addressed to personally identifiable information, and we do not distribute or share Ip information with any third parties.

We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes.

As our business continues to evolve, we may acquire or seW business units or subsidiaries. Customer information is one of the business assets that would be transferred in these types of transactions. In such a situation, your personaWy identifiable information would only be used in a manner consistent with our pre-existing Privacy Notice.We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.
